<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quizzes on the Holy Bible</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title">Quizzes on the Holy Bible</string>

    <!--Descriptions-->
    <string name="preface">The app contains questions and answers from the holy Bible prepared by the
        117th pope of Alexandria, Pope Shenouda III. Questions are categorized in 23 groups. Questions
        can be assessed by selecting from the navigation drawer or by clicking the next or previous buttons.
        Happy reading!</string>
    <string name="sample_question_text">This is where the question is displayed. The answer will also
    be displayed here when the user clicks answer button.</string>
    <string name="preface_body">Quizzing is a kind of spiritual recreation. it activates the memory
        and is a type of intellectual competition. It is useful in occupying time in Sunday schools,
        on picnics, in clubs, and on numerous other occasions. \n \nQuizzes on the Holy Bible has many
        advantages : \n \nThey provide information from the Bible; they link different pieces of information
        to each other, they draw the attention to certain fields of knowledge, and they are an incentive
        to the further acquisition of knowledge. \n \nThis book includes 366 Quizzes on the Holy Bible divided
        into various subjects to facilitate its use. The second part of this book consists of the answers
        to these questions. \n \nWe hope, by the grace of God, to follow this book with others, either other
        Quizzes on the Bible, or on Church history and the lives of the Saints, or other kinds of religious
        information. \n \nSo farewell till we meet in the other parts if by the grace of God it is His will
        and if He grants us life. \n \n Pope Shenouda III.</string>
    <string name="start_page">Start Page</string>
</resources>
